<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on GIS Enterprise Reporter</title>
    <link>https://yicongkuo.github.io/Notes/GIS-Enterprise-Reporter/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on GIS Enterprise Reporter</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language>
    <atom:link href="https://yicongkuo.github.io/Notes/GIS-Enterprise-Reporter/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the GIS Enterprise Reporter</title>
      <link>https://yicongkuo.github.io/Notes/GIS-Enterprise-Reporter/docs/01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yicongkuo.github.io/Notes/GIS-Enterprise-Reporter/docs/01/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the GIS Enterprise Reporter&#xD;#&#xD;A common challenge in administering an ArcGIS Enterprise system is the need document and/or otherwise communicate its design and configuration.&#xA;Typically, this is done by someone creating one or more diagrams. These diagrams sometimes have errors and/or omissions. And, they easily lose their relevance as the system changes. The underlying challenge is that the documentation of the system is not generated by the system itself, it reflects the understanding of one person at one moment in time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running GIS Enterprise Reporter, Tips &amp; Tricks</title>
      <link>https://yicongkuo.github.io/Notes/GIS-Enterprise-Reporter/docs/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yicongkuo.github.io/Notes/GIS-Enterprise-Reporter/docs/02/</guid>
      <description>Running GIS Enterprise Reporter, Tips &amp;amp; Tricks&#xD;#&#xD;The GIS Enterprise Reporter user interface is intended to have few options in the hopes that it is relatively straight-forward to execute.&#xA;In principle, you give it a Portal for ArcGIS &amp;ldquo;Target&amp;rdquo;, with an administrative credential for that Portal, tick some checkboxes, click &amp;ldquo;Execute&amp;rdquo;, and wait for it to complete.&#xA;There are some things that benefit from explanation. This article will offer information on the following topics:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making the Most of Services Outputs</title>
      <link>https://yicongkuo.github.io/Notes/GIS-Enterprise-Reporter/docs/03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://yicongkuo.github.io/Notes/GIS-Enterprise-Reporter/docs/03/</guid>
      <description>Making the Most of Services Outputs&#xD;#&#xD;Introduction&#xD;#&#xD;GIS Enterprise Reporter provides a lot of information about the content and configuration of an ArcGIS Enterprise. Among the outputs available is an &amp;ldquo;admin&amp;rdquo; Excel workbook. That workbook&amp;rsquo;s sheets contain information available from the Admin API&amp;rsquo;s of each server role in the ArcGIS Enterprise (Portal and all of the federated ArcGIS Server Sites). For each federated ArcGIS Server Site, there are several sheets that describe aspects of the services inventory.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
